Moving quickly along we've talked about a lot of basic words and prepositions.
快速前进，我们已经讨论了很多基本的单词和介词。
Let's just be clear about since ever since and until.
让我们清楚地了解从那时起和直到。
Because they're kind of the same idea when we use sense and ever since we have this beginning point
因为当我们使用感觉时它们的想法是一样的，自从我们有了这个起点
in the past and it's going until probably now and we'll continue in the future likely on until means
在过去，它可能会一直持续到现在，我们将在未来继续可能直到意味着
something was continuing before and it ends at some point doesn't have to be now.
有些事情以前一直在继续，它在某个时候结束，不一定是现在。
Doesn't have to be the future doesn't have to be the past but it could be any one of those now since
不一定是未来不一定是过去，但它可能是现在以来的任何一个
and ever since.
从那时起。
Can often be used in the same way especially if it's at the beginning of a sentence.
通常可以以相同的方式使用，尤其是在句首时。
We would say for example since since I was a little boy I've I've been interested in the moon and I
例如，我们会说，自从我还是个小男孩以来，我就对月球很感兴趣，而且我
could then say ever since I was a little boy I've been interested in the moon.
那么可以说，从我还是个小男孩的时候起，我就对月球很感兴趣。
We often use ever since when we're talking about events things that happen in time in the past that
自从我们谈论过去发生的事情以来，我们经常使用
have continued until the present.
一直持续到现在。
That's often how it's used.
这通常是它的使用方式。
Another example of ever since ever since.
从那时起的另一个例子。
Ever since my grandmother passed away.
自从我的祖母去世后。
That means died but passed away is often more polite.
这意味着死了但去世了往往更有礼貌。
I haven't been the same.
我一直不一样。
Now could we say since my grandmother passed away I haven't been the same.
现在我们可以说自从我祖母去世后我就变了。
Yeah.
是的。
You could say that but they're both events.
你可以这么说，但它们都是事件。
They're both things that happened in the past and they're focusing on some event not specifically some
它们都是过去发生的事情，它们专注于某些事件而不是特定的某些事件
time.
时间。
We often then use since only for time things and wouldn't use ever since so often for specific time
然后我们经常只在时间上使用since，而在特定时间里不会经常使用
things.
事物。
For example we wouldn't say ever since 2011.
例如，我们不会说自 2011 年以来。
We would more often say since 2011 but again it's a it's a small distinction.
自 2011 年以来，我们经常会说，但这又是一个很小的区别。
They're very very similar.
它们非常相似。
Let's look at a couple of examples of just since.
让我们看几个例子。
Let us do that since June.
让我们从六月开始这样做。
Since June things have been very strange.
自六月以来，事情一直很奇怪。
Maybe in a family or whatever since June things have been very strange.
也许在一个家庭或其他什么地方，自从六月以来，事情一直很奇怪。
We probably won't use ever since they're probably just use since June since June.
我们可能永远不会使用，因为它们可能只是从六月开始使用。
Or we could say for example I haven't eaten since 4 a. m..
或者我们可以说，例如我从凌晨 4 点起就没有吃过东西。米..
OK.
好的。
We would definitely won't use ever since here cannot work here can not use ever since I haven't eaten
我们绝对不会使用，因为这里不能工作，因为我没吃过，所以不能使用
ever since 4:00 AM.
从凌晨 4:00 开始。
That is incorrect.
这是不正确的。
We can use just since when we have this sentence structure and we mentioned a specific time like this.
我们可以使用 just since 当我们有这个句子结构并且我们提到了这样的特定时间。
OK.
好的。
So if we have a time of day then we won't use ever since again ever since can be used to focus on usually
因此，如果我们有一天中的某个时间，那么我们就不会再使用了，因为通常可以用来专注于
distant events in the past and to talk about some current condition.
遥远的过去发生的事情，谈谈现在的一些状况。
And when it began.
当它开始时。
Whereas senses used for simpler things.
而感官用于更简单的事情。
Let's look at one more example of since since Tuesday the office has been very quiet since Tuesday the
让我们再看一个例子，自周二以来，办公室一直非常安静。
office has been very quiet.
办公室一直很安静。
Now you could use ever since there you really could.
现在你可以使用，因为你真的可以。
But yeah again usually since we'll be used there because it's about a specific time.
但是是的，通常是因为我们会在那里使用，因为它是一个特定的时间。
It's just a bit more common.
它只是更常见一点。
So there is some overlap with sense and ever since.
因此，从那时起，与感觉有一些重叠。
But just to be clear this sort of thing when we're talking about a time of day especially in this sentence
但是，当我们谈论一天中的某个时间时，尤其是在这句话中，要清楚这种事情
structure we can not use ever since until.
从那以后我们就不能使用的结构。
I will stay until you ask me to leave.
我会一直待到你要我离开。
OK.
好的。
Pretty simple.
很简单。
That means when you say it's time for you to go.
这意味着当你说是时候离开了。
I will.
我会。
OK.
好的。
I will go if you don't say it.
你不说我就去。
I won't go.
我不会去的。
OK.
好的。
I will stay until you ask me to leave.
我会一直待到你要我离开。
We could take this out and we could just put a time here.
我们可以把它拿出来，我们可以在这里放一点时间。
I will stay until 10 p.m..
我会一直呆到晚上10点。。
Very simple very simple.
很简单很简单。
This is easy.
这很简单。
This is just the ending time.
这只是结束时间。
OK breakfast isn't served until 7:00 a.m. until 7:00 a.m..
OK 早餐直到早上 7:00 到早上 7:00 才供应。
Notice that sometimes we use time.
请注意，有时我们会使用时间。
Sometimes we can use days dates.
有时我们可以使用天数。
We can say months until June.
我们可以说直到六月。
It's not going to be ready until June.
它要到六月才能准备好。
I can't wait that long.
我不能等那么久。
That's three months from now.
那是从现在开始的三个月。
So that's the time in the future when it will happen.
所以那是将来发生的时候。
But time of day also works and events also work until you ask me to leave.
但是一天中的时间也有效，事件也有效，直到你让我离开。
OK.
好的。
She was very happy until John brought up her dead dog.
她非常高兴，直到约翰把她死去的狗带回来。
Then she started crying again.
然后她又开始哭了。
Or he was very sad until Cheryl came over and gave him a hug.
或者他很伤心，直到谢丽尔走过来给了他一个拥抱。
So you can talk about events too.
所以你也可以谈论事件。
OK.
好的。
Pretty simple pretty easy I think.
我认为很简单很容易。
I think you can probably understand as well.
我想你应该也能理解。
And I hope that you feel comfortable and confident to use since ever since and until.
我希望您从那时起一直感到舒适和自信地使用它。
And let's go on.
让我们继续吧。